MD. MAMUN MIA

Front-End Designer

Contact

- +8801878-036341
- Gazipur, Bangladesh.
- mamunahammedco59@gmail.com

I'm a Front-End Designer. I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work with 2+ year's experience as a professional Front-End Designer. I have completed 250+ websites that comply with the latest design trends. I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration. My quick coding skill helps me to finish the projects on time. I'm still learning and trying to add more skills.

EXPERIENCES

2021-2022 James Coders

Design and maintained code for in-house and client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and jQuery. Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness.

2020-2021 Clipping Quality Service

Worked with a team of three designers to convert psd to html, figma to HTML, xd to HTML. I have been building noteworthy UX/UI designs and websites for years, which comply with the latest design trends.



EDUCATION

2017-2022 Diploma In Computer Engineering

I completed my Diploma in Engineering from the Royal Institute of Technology (53042), Dhaka, Bangladesh.

2015–2017 SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

I completed my Secondary School Certificate from the Konabari M A Kuddus High School, Gazipur, Bangladesh.